In addition to looking at our trained model attributes,
除了查看训练过的模型的属性之外
we can also use those to deploy a PCA model and use it to make predictions.
我们还可以利用这些属性部署 PCA 模型并使用模型做出预测
To deploy a trained model,
为了部署训练过的模型
we simply call that model by name and call deploy.
我们通过名称调用该模型并调用 deploy()
Then we pass in a few details about the instance count one and instance type,
然后传入一些参数 将实例数量设为 1
which I'm using a t2 medium for the endpoint.
对于实例类型 端点将使用 ml.t2.medium
When I run this code, I can see that two things are automatically created.
运行这些代码后 可以看到系统自动创建了两项内容
First, a model with some name and an endpoint with some name.
包括具有特定名称的模型和具有特定名称的端点
Now, for built-in models,
对于内置模型来说
these two are often automatically created together.
这两项经常自动一起创建
But for some custom models as we'll see later,
但是对于我们稍后将见到的一些自定义模型
we'll have to separately create a model and then create an endpoint.
我们需要单独创建模型 然后创建端点
You could also consider using a different more powerful instance type,
你还可以考虑使用更强大的实例类型
but a t2 medium is going to be fine for our purposes.
但是对我们来说 t2 medium 足够了
This will take a few minutes to deploy, but once it does,
部署需要花费一段时间 部署完毕后
we can then use it applying it to our training data,
我们可以将模型应用到训练数据上
and transforming it into PCA components.
并将数据转换为 PCA 成分
In SageMaker, you have seen that an endpoint can be made accessible via a web app,
你已经知道在 SageMaker 中 我们可以将端点连接到 API Gateway
by attaching it to API Gateway.
使网络应用能访问端点
But in this case, we're just going to want to use
但是 现在我们将仅使用此预测器
this predictor to process our original training data,
处理原始训练数据
and create dimensionality reduced data.
并创建降维数据
Now that this predictor is deployed,
部署了预测器后
I can use it to modify our original training data.
我可以使用它修改原始训练数据
To apply endpoint to some data,
为了向数据应用端点
I just have to call.predict and pass in our training data.
我只需调用 .predict 并传入训练数据
This function is going to by default expect a NumPy array as input,
默认情况下 此函数要求输入是 NumPy 数组
and so I'm passing in the data that we converted before.
所以传入之前转换的数据
If you recall this, was just are scaled, normalized,
这些数据就是缩放范围并归一化的整洁 DataFrame
and cleaned DataFrame converted into a NumPy array.
再转换成 NumPy 数组
So this predict function is going to look at
predict() 函数将查看数据集中
the features of every data point in this set,
每个数据点的特征
and convert them into PCA components.
并将其转换成 PCA 成分
So this will hold the PCA component values
这个将存储原始 3,000 个左右
for each of our original 3,000 or so training points.
训练数据点的 PCA 成分值
Let's take a look at the first data point by printing it out by index, index zero.
我们看看第一个数据点的值 通过索引（索引为 0）输出信息
Though this is data for just one of our counties,
虽然这些数据仅针对某个郡县
I can see a key projection and a float 32 tensor.
但是可以看到 key: ”projection” 和 float_32 tensor
This holds our 33 component values.
该张量存储了 33 个成分值
As with the rest of our analyses,
与其他分析结果一样
the top components are actually going to be at the bottom of this list here.
前几位的成分实际上位于这个列表的底部
Now, using these names and this information about ordering,
下面请跟着这些名称和排序信息
I want you to create a transformed DataFrame.
创建一个转换后的 DataFrame
Specifically, I want you to complete the function create_transformed_df.
请完成函数 create_transformed_df
This will take in a list of our PCA training data that we just generated,
它的参数包括刚刚生成的 PCA 训练数据列表
our original county scale dataframe,
原始 counties_scale dataframe
and a number of top components.
以及 n_top_components
We need to create a DataFrame but still indexed by state county,
我们需要创建一个 DataFrame 依然以 State-County 为索引
but each column corresponds to one of these top end components.
但是每列都对应于前几位成分中的某个成分
So if this is seven top components,
如果这是前七位成分
you'll have seven columns of data.
你将看到 7 列数据
Your resultant DataFrame should look something like this.
生成的 DataFrame 应该是这样的
This function essentially creates a dataset where
这个函数会创建一个数据集
each county is described by the top and principal components,
其中每个郡县由前几位主成分描述
and it's exactly what we'll need to move on to K-means clustering.
这正是接下来的 K 均值聚类所需的数据集
So try to complete this function,
请试着完成此函数
and if you do, you can move on to the next steps,
完成后 请继续执行后面的步骤
which are deleting the PCA model endpoint that were done using,
包括使用完端点后 删除 PCA 模型端点
and moving onto training a K-means model on this new transformed data.
并使用新转换的数据训练 K 均值模型